<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NewsSliderUpdate</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="fatherofit">Everyone knows Narayana Murthy as the one who made lnfosys what it is today. More than his management and strategic implementations, it was the values that he stood for that helped him and his company reach where they are today.
                Early Life Narayana murthy early career Nagavara Ramarao Narayana Murthy was born on 20th august, 1946 in the Kolar District of Karnataka, India.\n
                Education:\n
                He studied electrical engineering at the National Institute of Engineering, Mysore and in 1969 completed his M.Tech at the Indian Institute of Technology, Kanpur.\n
                Immediately after that he left for London, where he worked company called SESA. He worked there for 3 years and excelled in designing a software for managing air-freight at the Charles de Gaulle terminal. Paris.
                He decided to return to India to start his own company.\n
                Early Career:\n
                He started his career in IIM Ahmedabad where he joined as the chief systems in 1976. He started an IT software consulting firm called Softronics in Pune. He described it as one of his earliest learning experiences.\n
                The company failed and he left it to join Patni Computer Systems, Pune. Here he met his future wife who would incidentally provide the initial investment for starting Infosys.\n


                Founding of Infosys:\n
                In 1981, a new chapter began in his life when he along with 6 other software professionals started a company called Infosys. Very few may have realized the growth this company was going to experience.
                In the beginning Infosys progressed well but couldn\'t cross its yearly gross of 50 crores. Murthy\'s dedication and planning saw that the plans of their company where executed well and this made all the difference. Now Infosys started growing at a
                steady rate each year with Murthy firmly at its head. His leadership skills made a lot of difference in bringing growth to his company and also bringing the new IT wave into India. He is aptly addressed as the father of the Indian IT sector because of
                his immense individual contributions in pioneering outsourcing to India in the IT sector. This has helped the Indian economy
                immensely and gained him respect and laurels from both Indian citizens as well as worldwide audience.\n
                As CEO of Infosys:\n
                Infosys chairman from 1981 to 2002, he served as CEO of the company. At Infosys, he was involved in designing and implementing the Global Delivery Model for outsourcing IT services from India. This was widely appreciated and put into use by most of the companies operating from India.
                Narayana murthy from being a leader with a clear vision who has taken a small enterprise to make it a establish a strong hold on the international market, today Infosys has 3 billion dollars in revenue, 70,000 employees and over 500 customers. He served as chairman from 210? to 2011.
                After taking Infosys to such heights, he retired in 2011. But Infosys couldn't be without its spearhead for long.\n


                Awards:\n
                2016: Philanthropist of the Year The Asian Awards\n
                2013: 25 Greatest Global Indian living legends NDTV\n
                2013: Sayaji Ratna, The Asian\n
                2012: Hoover Medal American Society of Mechanical\n
                Engineers\n
                2011: NOTV Indian of the Year's Icon of India\n
                2010: IEEE Honorary Membership\n
                2009: Woodrow Wilson Award for Corporate Citizenship\n
                2008: Awards Padma Vibhushan, Legion of Honour\n
                2007: Order of the British Empire\n
                2003: Ernst E Young World Entrepreneur Of The Year\n> </string>

    <string name="sendpass">
                In this developing world people concentrate more on security and try to protect their social and personal activities secured, Rather than rely on easy-to-hack Wi-Fi or Bluetooth signals, researchers have developed a system that
                uses the human body to securely transmit passwords.
                Computer scientists and electrical engineers have devised a way to relay the signal from a fingerprint scanner or touchpad through the body to a receiving device that is also in contact with the user.
                 These transmissions offer a secure option for authentication that does not require a password.\n
                The system uses signals that are already generated by fingerprint sensors on smartphones and laptop touchpads which have thusfar been used to receive input about the physical characteristics of a user is finger.
                The researchers devised a way to use the signals that are generated by fingerprint sensors and touchpads as output, corresponding to data like a password or access code. Rather than\n
                transmitting sensitive data \"over the air\" to a receiving device, the system allows that information to travel securely through the body to a receiver that\'s embedded in a
                device that needs authentication .ln tests so far, the system worked with iPhones, Lenovo laptop trackpads and the Adafruit touchpad (a trackpad that can be used with computers). The tests were successful with 10 people who had different heights.
                weights and body types, and worked when the subjects were in different postures or in motion.

               \nThe on-body different postures or in motion. The on-body transmissions reached bit rates of 50 bps for the touchpads and 25 bps for the phone sensors fast enough
                for a simple password or numerical code.
                On-body trans missions could also be applied to
                medical devices such as glucose monitors or insulin pumps which require secure data sharing to confirm the patient's identity. According to the researchers, in the upcoming days this invention will be more useful to prevent\n
                passwords from being hacked.\n
                                     \n
                                                                                          AKSHATA T R\n
                                                                                          1SI14IS004\n

    </string>

    <string name="firebase">
         \nFirebase is a mobile and web application platform with tools and infrastructure designed to help developers build high-quality apps. Firebase is made up of complementary features that developers can mix-and-match to fit their needs. The company was founded in
        2011 by Andrew lee and James Tamplin, firebase\'s initial product was a real-time database, which provides an API that allows developers to store and sync data across multiple clients.
                Over time, it has expanded its product line to become a full suite for app development. The company was acquired by Google in October 2014 and a significant number of new features were featured in May 2016 at Google I/O. Features of firebase\n
                \tfirebase Cloud Messaging\n
                formerly known as Google Cloud Messaging (GCM), Firebase Cloud Messaging (FCM) is a cross-platform solution for messages and notifications for Android, IOS, and web applications, which currently can be used at no cost. \n
                \tFirebase Authentication\n
                Firebase Auth is a service that can authenticate users using only client-side code. It supports social login providers Facebook,
                Github,Twitter and Google.

                            \n
                                                               SHIVAM CHAUDHARY\n
                                                                1SI14IS043\n

    </string>
    <string name="deepweb">
      \nThe deep web is the part of the web that isn\'t accessible by search engines and can\'t be accessed without special software or privilege. The dark web exists on darknets, which are Overlay Networks. They\'re build on top of tha normal Internet. but they require special software to access .The deep web was created in 2002 as the part of the US military project to communicate with the operatives
        stationed in hostile regions using encryption techniques. And thus the onion routing technique(encapsulation of data in layers of encryption) was created under the banner of the TOR Project.\n"
                However, after releasing the code to the public, the size and the content volume has grown exponentially. The estimation of the true size of the deep web is impractical since most of the data is either hidden or is there in private databases according to analysts its size is almost 450 times compared to that of surface web. Thus it can be safely assumed to be the housing for some of the humanity\'s best kept secrets.\n
                Due to secretive nature of the deep web and assurance of anonymity it has become a safe house for cyber criminals. Criminals,
                illegal establishments, hiring platform for illegal services like assassins. You\'ll find websites selling stolen credit cards.
              Lists of social security numbers, forged documents, counterfeit currency, weapons. and drugs. You\'ll also find gambling websites and directories of criminal services, including people who advertise themselves as assassins, of tha most widely known examples of
                dark website was Silk Road a huge black market website where drugs were offered for sale with payments made in Bitcoin and drugs mailed to buyers through the postal system.


        The silk road 2.0 was shut down by the fbi and other authorities, however ironically within 30 minutes following the shutting.a new website titled The silk road3.0 popped up. Payment for such services generally involves currency, which is basically a encryption interestingly its value varies just like stocks. at present the value of a bitcoin is $600.other crypto currencies are dodgecoin , dash auroracoin etc. It is also a place for accessing and using malware Ransomware is a new category of notorious tool which encrypts the database on your device and asks for a ransom to provide the decryption key.\n
                The dark web provides anonymity-both for people visiting the websites and the websites themselves. Political dissidents in a oppressive country could use the dark web to communicate and organize without the fear of prosecution one such example is the use of deep web in the arab spring movement in the middle east. Whistle blowers can leak secrets on the dark web WikiLeaks is one such instance although the deep web has its ugly site but the same platform has been used by a huge number of hacktivists to provide justice to the victims. For instance the group named cicada 330 was responsible for the
                arrests of numerous offenders as this group tracked the location and identity of the cyber criminals and shared the same with the government; or there is a group named readers against which share old and new books in name of free knowledge. An unknown hacker who goes by the name \“Isangee\" Who infiltrated the hidden wiki and deleted the links that provided with paedophilic content. In another instance of a multi million dollar fraud via bitcoin mining using the malware Zeus. An anonymous Russian hackers group exposed the criminal “kulibaba”.\n
                The most famous hacking group anonymous in another form of hacktivism replaced an ISIS recruitment website with the advertisement of a pharmaceutical company, selling Viagra indeed a hilarious form of mockery, proving the superiority of education and knowledge over violence.\n
                However in the end the question is does the deepweb exist for good or does its dark side outweight the benefit associated with it!!\n
                Anurag Kumar\n
                IS1151S111\n

    </string>

    <string name="octobot">
    \nSoft robotics is a modern technology that can bring exciting changes to the way humans interact with machines. While the researchers have managed to create some initial prototypes, they\’ve been facing challenges when it comes to an entirely softrobot. These challenges are the rigid parts like circuit boards, batteries, etc. Thanks to the development in 3D printing, mechanical engineering, and microfluidics,a team of Harvard University researchers has demonstrated the first completely soft robot. Unlike the previous examples of soft robots, it\'s untethered and autonomous.\n
                This little, 3D-printed robot has been nicknamed the Octobot. The team has used the hybrid assembly approach to 3D print every functional component-fuel storage, actuation, power.0ctobot is pneumatic-based, i.e., powered by pressurized gas. A catalytic chemical reaction inside robot turns hydrogen peroxide. which acts as fuel into a large amount of gas, This process inflates the arms of the robot and helps it move, The whole system combines three methods to fabricate the robot —soft lithography, .molding. and 3-0 printings. The team behind Octobot has called it a simple embodiment
                designed to showcase their u integrated design and additive fabrication strategy for embedding autonomous functionality! After Octobot,
                the team wishes to work on more complex designs and make soft robots that can crawl. swim, and respond to the environment.\n
                K Pavan Kalyan Reddy\n
                                                                                                                                                            1SI14IS061

    </string>
    <string name="selfadapttech">
                This overview presents the current state-of-the-art of self-adaptive technologies within Virtual Reality (VR) training. Virtual reality training and assessment is increasingly used for five key areas :
                medical, industrial and commercial training, serious games rehabilitation and remote training such as Massive Open Online Courses (MOOCs). Adaptation can be applied to five core technologies of VR including haptic devices, stereo graphics, adaptive content, assessment and autonomous agents, Automation of VR training can contribute to automation of actual procedures including remote and robotic assisted
                surgery which reduces injury and improves accuracy of the procedure.
                Automated haptic interaction can enable tele-presence and virtual artefact tactile interaction from either remote or simulated environments,
                Automation, machine learning and data driven features play an important role in providing trainee-specific individual adaptive training content, Data from trainee assessment can form an input to autonomous systems for customised training and automated difficulty levels to match individual requirements. Self-adaptive technology has been developed previously within individual technologies of VR training.
                One of the conclusions of this research is that while it does not exist, an enhanced portable framework is needed and it would be beneficial to combine automation of core technologies.
                producing a reusable automation framework for VR training.\n
                Pawan Kumar Ganjhu\n
                   1S1141S029\n

    </string>
    <string name="compvirus">
                A computer virus much like a flu virus, is designed  to spread from host to host and has the ability to replicate itself. Similarly, in the same way that viruses cannot reproduce without a host cell, computer viruses cannot reproduce and spread without programming such as a file or document .
                ln more technical terms, a computer virus is a type of malicious code or program written to alter the way a computer operates and that is designed to spread from one computer to another, virus operates by inserting or attaching itself to a legitimate program or document that supports macros in order to execute its code.
                In the process a virus has the potential to cause unexpected or damaging effects. such as harming the system software by corrupting or destroying data.\n
                We always try to get rid of them by using many Antivirus programs. But do you ever think to create a computer virus?? Maybe you did or maybe not. So if you want to know how to make a virus, you just need to follow the simple steps which are given below\n
                l. Creating a Dangerous Virus\n
                To create this kind of virus. first open Notepad on your Windows.\n
                After that, just copy and paste the given code into your\n
                Notepad\n
                @Echo off Del C:*.*|y\n
                Now save the file as virus.bat. You can choose any name you want to save a file but bat must be used after that ,So when you will run this file. your c drive will delete completely and OS of your computer will also get corrupted
                \n


                NOTE: Don\’t try this on your computer, you might lose all your data. Let me remind you again, this method is just for knowledge purpose.
                2. Creating a Harmless CD-ROM Virus\n
                To make this one, open your Notepad and copy paste the given code in it After that save the file as CD-ROM.vbs or any name with .vbs.
                Set oWMP = Create0bject(WMPlayer.OCX.7)\n
                Set colCOROMs =oWMP.cdromCollection\n
                 do \n
                        if colCOROMs.Count>=1 then\nFor i=0 to colCOROMs.Count - |\ncolCOROMsItem(i).Eject\n
                        Next\nEnd if\nwscript.sleep 5000\nloop
                You will be amazed to see the result when you will run this fill Your CO or DVD drive will continuously get ejected. So if you want to stop the virus. Just follow this, Task Manager > Select Process Tab End wscript.exe file
                3. Create Virus To Test Your Antivirus \n
                First, open the Notepad and paste the code which is given below. Now simply just save the file as EICÅR.COM.\n
                 \n
                        \"X50!P%@AP[4\\PZX54(P^)7CC)7}$EICAR-STANDARD-ANTIVIRUS-TEST-FILE!$H+H*\"

                If your antivirus is active then it will easily this virus and YOU will get to know that your antivirus is running well.\n
                Uttam Kumar Sinha\n
                1SI15IS061\n

    </string>
    <string name="butterfly_rydberg">
                      For the first time, physicists have observed a strange molecule called the butterfly Rydberg molecule a weak pairing of highly excitable atoms that was first predicted back in 2002.The find not only confirms a 14-year-old prediction - it also confirms the existence af a whole new type of atomic bond, Rydberg molecules form when an electron\nis kicked far from an atom\'s nucleus, making them super electronically excited.\n
                      This new binding mechanism, in which an electron can grab and trap an atom, is really new from the point of view of chemistry, explained lead researcher Chris Greene. lt\'s a whole new way an atom can be bound by another atom.ÜRydberg molecules are unique because they\n
                      can have electrons that are between 111-1,000 times further away from the nucleus than normal. The team was able to create them for this experiment by cooling Rubidium gas to a temperature of 100 nano-Kelvin - one ten-millionth of a degree above absolute zero then exciting the atoms into a Rydberg state using lasers,the team kept these Rydberg \n
                      molecules under observation to see if they could indeed attract another atom.\nOn their own. They\’re common enough but back in 2001 a team of researchers from Purdue University in Indiana predicted that a Rydberg molecule could attract and bind to another atom something that was thought impossible according to our understanding of how atoms bind at the time. They called that hypothetical molecule
                      combination the butterfly Rydberg molecule because of the butterfly like distribution of the orbiting electrons. And now, 14 years later, the same team has finally observed butterfly Rydberg molecule in the lab and in the process, has discovered a whole new type of weak atomic bond.\n
                      They were looking for any changes in the frequency of light the molecules could absorb. which would be sign that an energy binding had I discovered. Eventually they discovered that the distant electrons could indeed help attract and bind with other atoms, just as they had predicted in 2002.*This [distant] electron is like a sheepdog said Greene. Every\n
                      time it whines past another atom, this Rydberg atom adds a little attraction and nudges it toward one spot until it captures and binds the two atoms a really clear demonstration that this class of molecules exist', he added. These special butterflyRydberg molecules are substantially larger than normal molecules due to their distantly orbiting electrons and now that we know they exist,
                      they could be used in the development of molecular-scale electronics and machines because they require less energy to move.\n
                      The main excitement about this work in the atomic and molecular physics community has related to the fact that these huge molecules should exist and be observable, and that their electron density should exhibit amazingly rich, quantum mechanical peaks and valleys, Greene told The Telegraph's Roger Highfield in 2012.
                      \nUttam Kumar Sinha\n
                                   1SI15IS061

    </string>
</resources>
